Hs rewinds itself again as the go words are written
I think it's probably the other gender so we're at the $16 I just I was I was a leader on 5g getting that
and now they're up to six.
What does that do?
Give you a little bit deeper view
into somebody's skin.
I like the cameras the old days.
So they just had a nice feature.
Investment in this kind of technology
has been going on for years,
all with one goal,
to protect the soldiers protecting us.
What we do is we say,
well, the science is interesting,
but
We're translating that we're translating that into application and benefit and
It's something frankly. I think the Department of Defense does really really well
We can see science, but we
mission. We have net. We'v
mission. In March of 2020,
made headlines when more t
tested positive for covid
the outbreak kept the ship
4800 sailors from their m
nation. Dr Matthew Hepburn
his entire career to preve
what we want to do is detect an infection as early as possible before someone even spreads it to another person.
to try to prevent that in
so that it never happens.
we detect and treat. And
might want to do is then
else is protected. That d
thanks to this tiny hydra
placed under the skin. It
on at a tissue level. For
of lactate in your body.
is a really good indicator that someone is starting to get sick.
Now they cover every little. Let's see, Michael, you're in good shape. You're not going to...
But I tell you, it's... So you're... The six is coming, huh?
It's gone. Does it ever end? And what happens?
You'll be into seven, right? Before six gets old, you'll be into seven.
It's one of those things that we see go up pretty early in severe infection.
called sepsis. The sensor doesn't identify what infection you might have.
It's more of an alert. Hepburn compares it to a check engine light. Like a
check engine light doesn't say that there's a problem you're out of oil or
something like that. It just says there's something wrong. There may be
something wrong with your engine so take a closer look. Leveraging the
transformative 7 gigahertz upper mid-band spectrum.
Our 256 TRX massive MIMO radio and VRan architecture unlock the potential for unprecedented data speeds.
Using the massive MIMO radio with VRan, we achieved downlink throughput of 3.05 Giga BPS,
with 100 MHz of spectrum in the 7 Giga Hertz band,
accomplished via an 8-layer MIMO downlink transmission for a single user.
be a part of the next evolution in motion pictures and experience mind gamers being
hailed as the first